=The Queen of Attack=
=ملكة الهجوم=
=Episode 21=
=الحلقة 21=
I suddenly realize
أدركت فجأة
that if you were pregnant with Xiao Xian's child
أنه إذا كنت حاملاً بطفل شياو شيان
and claimed it's Prince Rui's...
وزعم أنها للأمير روي.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
you...
أنت...
You're insane.
أنت مجنون.
Then why not just make Xiao Xian the heir?
إذن لماذا لا نجعل شياو شيان الوريث؟
No!
لا!
On what grounds?
على أي أساس؟
If he inherits the title,
إذا ورث اللقب،
his lowborn father
والده الوضيع
would move into the mansion.
سوف ينتقل إلى القصر.
He'd strut around looking down on me.
كان يتبختر حولي وينظر إلي.
He doesn't deserve that.
إنه لا يستحق ذلك.
Xiao Xian
شياو شيان
will never inherit the throne.
لن يرث العرش أبدًا.
As for you,
أما بالنسبة لك،
I have my own plans.
لدي خططي الخاصة.
Perhaps you aren't fully aware
ربما لا تكون على علم كامل
of the true identity of the monster
عن الهوية الحقيقية للوحش
who bit you in the death cell.
من عضك في زنزانة الموت؟
To captivate a man,
لأسر الرجل،
you should use the left one.
ينبغي عليك استخدام اليسار.
Master,
يتقن،
why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
You're my disciple.
أنت تلميذي.
I didn't teach you properly
لم أعلمك بشكل صحيح
about these incenses.
حول هذه البخور.
Aphrodisiac incenses.
البخور المثير للشهوة الجنسية.
I never thought we'd use them.
لم أكن أعتقد أبدًا أننا سنستخدمها.
But since you need it,
ولكن بما أنك بحاجة إليها،
learn thoroughly.
تعلم جيدا.
There's no need.
ليست هناك حاجة.
This one suits you best.
هذا يناسبك بشكل أفضل.
It truly kindles desire
إنه يثير الرغبة حقًا
by awakening buried feelings.
من خلال إيقاظ المشاعر المدفونة.
If you feel nothing,
إذا لم تشعر بشيء،
it remains powerless.
ويظل عاجزًا.
But if feelings exist,
ولكن إذا كانت المشاعر موجودة،
you'll lose self-control.
سوف تفقد السيطرة على نفسك.
Master,
يتقن،
why are you lighting it?
لماذا تضيئه؟
We've always been open with each other.
لقد كنا دائمًا منفتحين مع بعضنا البعض.
Why afraid?
لماذا خائف؟
What are you afraid of?
ماذا تخاف منه؟
You.
أنت.
Master.
يتقن.
Linlang.
لينلانغ.
Do you truly know yourself?
هل تعرف نفسك حقا؟
Let's use this incense to reveal your true heart.
دعونا نستخدم هذا البخور للكشف عن قلبك الحقيقي.
He's here.
إنه هنا.
Who is there?
من هناك؟
I'm sleeping.
أنا نائمة.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I'll be your Mother Consort.
سأكون زوجتك وأمك.
Mother Consort?
زوجة الأم؟
Why did you come suddenly?
لماذا أتيت فجأة؟
I heard the County Princess gave you trouble today.
سمعت أن أميرة المقاطعة سببت لك مشكلة اليوم.
She lured you here?
هل أغوتك إلى هنا؟
Why would she do that?
لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
She wants...
إنها تريد...
Wants what?
يريد ماذا؟
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
You should leave.
ينبغي عليك أن تغادر.
I know exactly what the County Princess intends.
أنا أعلم تمامًا ما تقصده أميرة المقاطعة.
She's hated my father since young.
لقد كرهت والدي منذ الصغر.
Their feud has lasted a lifetime.
لقد استمر عداءهم مدى الحياة.
Even with the vilest methods,
حتى مع أبشع الأساليب،
she'll never let me inherit the title.
لن تسمح لي أبدًا بالحصول على اللقب.
She even wants us to...
حتى أنها تريد منا أن...
Shut your mouth.
اصمت.
The incense.
البخور.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
I won't do anything to you.
لن أفعل لك أي شيء.
Remember.
يتذكر.
Whatever threats she makes,
مهما كانت التهديدات التي تطلقها،
don't yield.
لا تستسلم.
Don't act recklessly.
لا تتصرف بتهور.
I've already owed you too much.
لقد كنت مدينًا لك كثيرًا بالفعل.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
leave it to me.
اتركها لي.
Absolutely not.
بالتأكيد لا.
You said it yourself.
لقد قلت ذلك بنفسك.
She ordered me to come tonight,
لقد أمرتني أن آتي الليلة،
so there must be guard outside.
لذلك يجب أن يكون هناك حارس بالخارج.
If I stay here overnight,
إذا بقيت هنا طوال الليل،
you can report success.
يمكنك الإبلاغ عن النجاح.
If she threatens you again,
إذا هددتك مرة أخرى،
you'll have a proper excuse.
سيكون لديك عذر مناسب.
Watch out!
احذر!
What are you...
ماذا انت...؟
I can't stay awake all night,
لا أستطيع البقاء مستيقظا طوال الليل،
right?
يمين؟
Move.
يتحرك.
S-So you're not worried about me?
س-لذا فأنت لست قلقًا علي؟
I have bigger concerns.
لدي مخاوف أكبر.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Go extinguish the candles.
اذهب لإطفاء الشموع.
Okay.
تمام.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Last night, you lit incense.
لقد أشعلت البخور الليلة الماضية.
But you showed no feelings toward him.
ولكنك لم تظهر أي مشاعر تجاهه.
Do you understand
هل تفهم
your heart now?
قلبك الآن؟
And what about your heart,
وماذا عن قلبك؟
Master?
يتقن؟
You've always stayed by my side, protecting me.
لقد بقيت دائمًا بجانبي، تحميني.
Master.
يتقن.
Do you want me?
هل تريدني؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
You know what I desire most.
أنت تعرف ما أرغب فيه أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
All my enemies have received their due punishments.
لقد تلقى جميع أعدائي عقوبتهم المستحقة.
But what about me?
ولكن ماذا عني؟
Why can't I just be Lin Hong'er?
لماذا لا أستطيع أن أكون لين هونغ إير فقط؟
Why must I never be Lin Hong'er again?
لماذا لا يجب أن أكون لين هونغ إير مرة أخرى؟
Because you refuse to testify for me.
لأنك ترفض أن تشهد لي.
Because of your secrets from the past,
بسبب أسرارك من الماضي،
you can't let anyone know you can cure Gu poison.
لا يمكنك إخبار أي شخص أنك قادر على علاج السم Gu.
Because
لأن
you were the first one poisoned.
لقد كنت أول شخص مسموم.
Your face changed.
وجهك تغير.
You can't let anyone discover
لا يمكنك السماح لأحد باكتشاف
that the old version of you still lives.
أن النسخة القديمة منك لا تزال تعيش.
You investigated me?
هل حققت معي؟
Master,
يتقن،
I'm someone who returned from death.
أنا شخص عاد من الموت.
I've long abandoned hope for love or affection.
لقد تخليت منذ فترة طويلة عن الأمل في الحب أو المودة.
Gratitude and loyalty must stay buried in my heart for now.
يجب أن يبقى الامتنان والولاء مدفونين في قلبي الآن.
Because I have greater unfinished business.
لأن لدي أعمال أكبر لم أنتهي منها.
You taught me so much.
لقد علمتني الكثير.
I've schemed and strategized every step of the way.
لقد خططت ووضعت استراتيجية لكل خطوة على الطريق.
How could I let the County Princess threaten me?
كيف يمكنني السماح لأميرة المقاطعة بتهديدي؟
I can agree to your terms,
يمكنني الموافقة على شروطك،
but I have my own conditions.
ولكن لدي شروطي الخاصة.
Conditions?
شروط؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
you weren't surprised at all by my changed appearance.
لم تفاجأ على الإطلاق بمظهري المتغير.
Nor were you shocked by the existence of that monster.
ولم تصدم من وجود هذا الوحش.
Because you already knew.
لأنك عرفت بالفعل.
You knew his grotesque form was due to Gu poison,
لقد عرفت أن شكله الغريب كان بسبب سم جو،
rotting his flesh into that monstrous shape.
تعفن لحمه إلى هذا الشكل الوحشي.
And you also knew
وعرفت أيضا
that curing this poison
أن علاج هذا السم
would permanently alter one's appearance.
من شأنه أن يغير مظهر الشخص بشكل دائم .
So, Your Highness,
لذا، صاحب السمو،
you can verify
يمكنك التحقق
and confirm my identity.
وتأكيد هويتي.
I do know about Gu poison,
أنا أعرف عن السم جو،
and I can help prove
ويمكنني المساعدة في إثبات ذلك
that this poison drastically alters one's looks.
أن هذا السم يغير مظهر الإنسان بشكل جذري.
I can even restore
حتى أنني أستطيع استعادة
your original face.
وجهك الأصلي.
But first, I must meet the one who cured you.
ولكن أولاً، يجب أن أقابل الشخص الذي شفاك.
I swapped the incense.
لقد قمت بتبديل البخور.
It drains internal energy.
فهو يستنزف الطاقة الداخلية.
Master, you refuse to testify for me.
يا سيدي، أنت ترفض أن تشهد لي.
Yet in this world,
ولكن في هذا العالم،
you're the only one who can prove my innocence.
أنت الوحيد الذي يستطيع إثبات براءتي.
This matters to me more than anything.
هذا يهم بالنسبة لي أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
The injustice Lin Hong'er suffered...
الظلم الذي عانت منه لين هونغ إير...
I'll clear it myself as Lin Hong'er.
سأقوم بتوضيح ذلك بنفسي باعتباري لين هونغ إير.
Master,
يتقن،
as you said,
كما قلت
this game
هذه اللعبة
will only grow more thrilling.
سوف تصبح أكثر إثارة فقط.
Can you truly change my face back?
هل يمكنك حقا تغيير وجهي مرة أخرى؟
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
Shentu Yu suppressed the poison for you,
لقد قمعت شنتو يو السم من أجلك،
but he can't cure it.
ولكنه لا يستطيع علاجه.
Only I possess the antidote,
أنا وحدي أملك الترياق،
because this poison
لأن هذا السم
was brewed by me.
تم تحضيره بواسطتي.
This needle will block his Qi and blood,
هذه الإبرة سوف تمنع تشي ودمه،
slow his reflexes,
إبطاء ردود أفعاله،
and cloud his mind.
وتغيم على عقله.
That way,
بهذه الطريقة،
extracting answers from him will be easier.
استخراج الإجابات منه سيكون أسهل.
Truly, a master's excellence shapes the disciple.
حقا إن تميز المعلم يشكل التلميذ.
The problem with him
المشكلة معه
is that he's too clever.
إنه ذكي للغاية.
If he were a bit duller,
لو كان أكثر مللاً بعض الشيء،
things would go much smoother.
الأمور سوف تسير بشكل أكثر سلاسة.
Now,
الآن،
it's time to restore my face.
حان الوقت لاستعادة وجهي.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
The process
العملية
is excruciating.
أمر مؤلم للغاية.
You're back.
لقد عدت.
Father?
أب؟
Mother?
الأم؟
Linlang?
لينلانغ؟
Master,
يتقن،
the County Princess restored my face.
لقد قامت أميرة المقاطعة بترميم وجهي.
Lin Hong'er?
لين هونغ إير؟
Do you still recognize me?
هل لازلت تعرفني؟
Master.
يتقن.
- Master. - Hong'er.
- سيد. - هونغ'ر.
Hong'er.
هونغ'ر.
Master.
يتقن.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I...
أنا...
I am Shentu Yu.
أنا شنتو يو.
Don't lie to me.
لا تكذب علي.
I know your heart.
انا اعرف قلبك.
You love me.
كنت تحبني.
You've always loved me.
لقد أحببتني دائمًا.
Just tell me the truth,
فقط قل لي الحقيقة
and we can be together.
ونستطيع أن نكون معاً.
I...
أنا...
I am the former Crown Prince.
أنا ولي العهد السابق.
♪Fate begins and ends, I sip the past♪
???القدر يبدأ وينتهي، أنا أرتشف الماضي؟؟؟
♪Love and hatred flow endlessly♪
???الحب والكراهية يتدفقان بلا نهاية؟؟؟
♪When spring comes, I see the truth♪
???عندما يأتي الربيع أرى الحقيقة؟؟؟
♪We've changed through the years♪
???لقد تغيرنا عبر السنين؟؟؟
♪Cold lamps reflect pear blossom dew♪
???المصابيح الباردة تعكس ندى زهرة الكمثرى ???
♪Worlds change as streams run west♪
???تتغير العوالم عندما تتدفق المجاري المائية غربًا؟؟؟
♪Rains veil hills, gathering sorrows♪
???أمطار تحجب التلال، وتجمع الأحزان؟؟؟
♪In deep courtyards, hands drift apart♪
???في الساحات العميقة، تتباعد الأيدي؟؟؟